<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Chic0s</title>
    <link>https://Chic0s.fr/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Chic0s</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 21:23:42 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Chic0s.fr/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Jwt Token</title>
      <link>https://Chic0s.fr/posts/jwt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 21:23:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Chic0s.fr/posts/jwt/</guid>
      <description>What is JWT Token ? A JSON Web Token (JWT) consists of three parts separated by periods (.): the header, the payload, and the signature. Each part is Base64-encoded.
Example JWT:  Header:  { &amp;#34;alg&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;HS256&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;typ&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;JWT&amp;#34; } Encoded in Base64, the header becomes: eyJhbGciOiAiSFMyNTYiLCAidHlwIjogIkpXVCJ9
Payload:  { &amp;#34;sub&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;1234567890&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;name&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;John Doe&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;iat&amp;#34;: 1516239022 } Encoded in Base64, the payload becomes:
eyJzdWIiOiAiMTIzNDU2Nzg5MCIsICJuYW1lIjogIkpvaG4gRG9lIiwgICJpYXQiOiAxNTE2MjM5MDIyfQ Signature: The signature is generated using the algorithm specified in the header (here, &amp;ldquo;HS256&amp;rdquo;).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keyboard with RubberDucky</title>
      <link>https://Chic0s.fr/posts/keyboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 16:44:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Chic0s.fr/posts/keyboard/</guid>
      <description>Integration of a Rubber Ducky into a USB Keyboard Objective: We are increasingly faced with the presence of dangerous USB keys. However, keyboards can also be a means of injecting malicious code into your computer. We will see how to create a keyboard with a Rubber Ducky. Nevertheless, for security reasons, no code will be disclosed.
Hardware Firstly, a soldering set will be necessary, and you need some basic skills to complete this project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proxmark 3</title>
      <link>https://Chic0s.fr/posts/proxmark3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 16:44:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Chic0s.fr/posts/proxmark3/</guid>
      <description>1 - Implementation of the Tool In the first step, I will equip myself with my tool:
The Proxmark 3 Easy, you can find this little gadget on AliExpress for around 50€. It has two antennas, one for low frequency and one for high frequency.
To use it, you will need a tool called Iceman. YouTube tutorial for updating the firmware and installing Iceman: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=n1Xt-1ZmjM0&amp;amp;feature=emb_imp_woyt
2 - Identifying the Badge To identify the badge, we will use the &amp;lsquo;auto&amp;rsquo; command, which allows scanning across different frequencies (high and low frequencies).</description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
